lightspeedvt.com 2017-09-03

# Privacy Policy | LightSpeed VT Interactive Virtual Training System

We take privacy issues seriously. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. **LightSpeed VT** is referred to as “THIS SITE” in the rest of this document. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.

Why do we collect personal information?

THIS SITE collects personal information to improve the manner by which we operate, offer our products and services, communicate with you about those products and services, and provide effective, timely customer support when needed. We will never rent or sell any of the personal information we collect from you to third parties, and we do not share your personal information except as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

What kind of personal information do we collect?

This site collects personal information in a variety of ways when you interact with this site, including when you register or create an account with THIS SITE; when you place an order at THIS SITE; when you use THIS SITE’s products or services; when you enter promotions or sweepstakes; when you subscribe to a newsletter or desire to be added to our mailing lists for other products or services; when you correspond or otherwise interact with us; and when you provide feedback in any of our online surveys. Information we collect may include: your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, product preference information, billing information, demographic information provided by you (such as language, gender and age, and, if applicable, content preferences and personalization information) and personal interest information. On occasion, we may ask for additional information to enable us to provide you with access to and use of certain information, materials and services. What other kinds of information do we collect? THIS SITE automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, information about which pages you visit on THIS SITE, and information from cookies.

What are cookies and how do we use them?

Cookies are small data files that write to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit a website. Cookies allow THIS SITE to measure traffic activity as well as to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences. Like other major websites, THIS SITE uses cookies to provide you with a tailored experience when visiting THIS SITE and using our products. We treat any personal information that may be contained in cookies with the same level of confidentiality as other information you provide to us. If you wish to disable cookie functionality, you may do so by changing the security settings on your browser. However, portions of THIS SITE may not function or function as efficiently, without them.

How do we protect your personal information?

THIS SITE safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. To make purchases from THIS SITE, you must use an SSL-enabled browser. THIS SITE uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on web pages used to complete a purchase. This protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet. THIS SITE takes precautions to ensure the security of your data, no one can completely guarantee the safety of data transmitted over the internet. It is important that you take steps to ensure the safety and security of your personal information, for example by not sharing passwords or other registration data.

How and when do we disclose the information we collect?

THIS SITE may send personal information about you to other companies or people when we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested, or to provide a product or service to you. However, these companies are only permitted to use the personal information for these purposes.

THIS SITE may also disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with law or legal process or if requested by duly authorized public authorities; (b) comply with the order of a competent judicial authority in any jurisdiction; (c) comply with legal process served on.
